明天是VOLAI180号航班…
Tomorrow marks the one year anniversary
坠机爆炸一周年纪念日
since Velez Air Flight 180 exploded and crashed
此航班是在JFK机场起飞后不久发生坠毁的
shortly after takeoff from JFK Airport.
这次灾难波及多人
It's a disaster that's affected many.
最严重的应该算是亚伯拉罕高中
None more so than Mt Abraham High School,
共有40名学生和4名教师丧生
which lost 40 students and four faculty members in the crash.
但灾难后发生的事情
But it was the events after the crash
使这场悲剧变得却更加离奇
that has turned this tragic story into something even stranger.
那些在坠机前侥幸逃脱的幸存者
The survivors who managed to get off the plane before it crashed
很快死于一系列
died soon thereafter in a series
神秘离奇的事故
of mysterious and bizarre accidents.
对一些人来说 这只是悲剧性的巧合
Now,to some,these deaths are just tragic coincidences,
但对另一些人来说 却预示着
but to others,they're an indication
某种不祥的事情即将发生
that there are more sinister events taking place.
这就是今晚嘉宾们要讨论的话题
That's the contention of tonight's guest.
谢谢你们的参与
Thank you for joining us this evening.
谢谢你邀请我来
Thank you for having me.
我很喜欢你用的"不祥"一词
And I appreciate you using the word sinister.
大多数人都说是"超自然"
Most people say supernatural because they think I'm talking
因为他们以为我谈论的是"鬼魂"
about ghosts and witches and stuff like that.
请直接谈论这个话题
Here's your chance to set the record straight.
好的 没问题
Great. Okay.
我认为有某种力量
I believe that there's a sort of force,
一种看不见的可怕的东西…
an unseen malevolent presence...
整天都围绕在我们的周围
that's all around us every day.
就是这种东西导致了人们的苦难和死亡
And it determines when we live and die.
有些人称之为"魔鬼的力量"
And some people call this force the devil,
不过我认为这有点宗教化了…
but I think that whole religious thing is...
我宁愿称之为"死亡"
so I prefer to call it Death itself.
那么按照你看法 我们被死亡包围?
So I'm surrounded by Death?
是的 没错
Absolutely. Absolutely.
是的 每天 每时 无处不在
Every day,everywhere,all the time.
我想大家知道…
And that's what I want people to understand...
死亡对我们每个人
that Death has this grand design
都有适合他自己的设计
that we all fit into.
当布朗宁从飞机上…
So when Alex Browning got off that plane
救走那些生还者
and took the other survivors with him,
实际上他是破坏了死亡的设计
he basically screwed up Death's plan.
这就是我要警告大家的
And that's what I'm trying to warn people about.
所有的幸存者都已经死去…
And the fact that all of the survivors have died
就是你的证据吗?
is your evidence of this?
这不是生还者死不死的问题
Well,it's not so much that the survivors died,
而是这些人是怎么死的
but it's the way that they died.
我是说他们死得那么奇怪
I mean,there were so many weird,
或者说看上去随意
seemingly random things about the way they died.
根本无法解释
It just didn't make sense.
这就证明了确实有某种力量存在…
And that's the proof there's something out there...
等等 这不是证据 这只是你的一面之词
Wait,that's not proof. That is your interpretation
你这样说只是为了证明你的观点 对吗?
of events that can't be proven in order to support your ideas.
凯柏莉
Kimberly.
你的思想应该开放点…
You should be more open-minded...
任何事都是可能的 那些只是巧合罢了
What happened after that was just coincidence.
能让我说完吗?
May I finish?
巧合只会让一两个人死亡
Mere coincidence would have one or two of these kids die.
而不会让这些人包括他们的老师都死去
But not all of them including their teachers.
是的 任何时候都有人死去
Yes,but people die all the time,
这次又有何不同?
so why should this be any different?
这就迫使大家…
It forced people to question
都对日常的巧合产生了疑问
these so-called everyday coincidences.
如果这背后隐藏着什么怎么办?
What if they were something more?
是不是我们能做些什么呢?
What if you could do something about it?
你听听你自己 你简直疯了
Please,are you listening to yourself? This is crazy.
我们每天早晨离家后 都得小心翼翼?
You're saying we should be on guard every morning when we leave the house?
对 我就是此意
That's exactly what I'm saying.
就是这个
Exactly it.
为了逃过此劫…
And in order to survive...
唯一的方法
the only way to survive
就是看到隐藏在这个可见的世界下面的东西
is to look beneath the visible world.
因为没有人可以躲避死亡
Because in the end no one can escape death.
也许今天你就是你的死期
And today may be your day to die.
好了 我会给你电话的
Okay,I'll call you.
凯柏莉 什么都带齐了吗?
Kimberly,are you sure you've got everything?
信用卡 手机 3A卡?
Credit card,cell phone,Triple-A card?
老爸啊 我是去玳多纳 可不是去索马里
Dad,it's Daytona,not Somalia.
补胎胶 防晒霜 催泪喷雾?
Alright. Fix-a-flat,road flares,sunblock,mace?
避孕套 鞭子 铁链
Condoms,whips,chains.
开个玩笑 卡曼先生
Just kidding,Mr Corman.
别担心 我会照看她的
Don't worry,I'll keep an eye on her.
你这样说 我就放心了 多谢
That makes me feel a lot better,thanks.
- 好吧 - 好的
- Okay. - Alrighty.
我们快去带上那些家伙吧 我等不及了
Can we go get the guys? I'm getting horny.
上路吧
Go on.
好的 我会打电话给你
Okay,I'll call you.
鞭子 铁链 你真会说
Whips and chains. That's nice.
不管你怎么说 你老爸对你真够好的
Whatever,your dad's cool.
系好安全带
Buckle up!
小心
Watch it!
- 别担心 凯米 头一次开车? - 抱歉
- Oh,easy,Kimmy. First year of driving? - Sorry.
- 天哪 上帝 - 老年痴呆
- Oh my God. - Fucking freak.
噢 丹尼尔 要不要帮帮你妈妈?
Yo,Dano,shouldn't we help your mum?
好孩子 你去吧 没人阻拦的
Good one,man. You're hilarious.
你是说不到我的
You're not getting any of my weed. Nothing.
管你怎么说
Whatever.
我们去玳多纳做什么呢?
What are we going to do in Daytona?
啊 我们可以看见很多小妞
We're going to see lots of honeys there.
可以喝酒 吸烟
We're gonna get drunk,we're gonna smoke this bigEl Gagerero,
在海滩上搞派对…
We're gonna have this awesome party...
连环相撞 连环相撞
Pileup! Pileup!
180号飞机
A candlelight vigil to mark the one year anniversary
空难周年纪念今晚8点
of the crash of Flight 180 will be held at 8:00 P.M. Tonight
在亚伯拉罕中学礼堂举行
at the Mt Abraham high school auditorium.
通往地狱的高速公路
Highway to hell...
我的天啊
Oh my God.
- 喂? - 嗨 凯柏莉 我是爸爸
- Hello? - Hey,Kimberly,it's Dad.
- 是的 什么事? - 你的传输器漏油了
- Hey,what's up? - Your car's leaking transmission fluid.
- 立即检查一下 - 好的
- So I want you to get it checked right away. - Okay,yeah.
我会的
I'll do that.
小心点
I mean it. Take care of it.
- 有人咳嗽吗? - 是的 没事的
- Is that someone coughing? - Yeah,okay.
是的 我会处理的 回头见
I'll take care of it. I'll talk to you later.
- 我爱你 - 再见 亲爱的
- I love you. - Bye,honey.
- 你干什么了? - 看那大胸脯!
- What did you do? - Look at those titties!
- 闭嘴! - 你没看到?
- Shut up. - You missed that?!
太可惜了 太可惜了
That's too bad. That's too bad.
噢 见鬼!
Oh,shit!
妈的 有警察 快到右道
Fuck man,there's a cop behind us! Pull in the right lane now!
见鬼
Shit.
我是说真的 把烟丢掉
Seriously,put it out.
- 快丢掉 - 好的
- Put that thing out. - Alright.
等等 等等 等等
Wait,wait,wait!
- 快扔掉 - 见鬼
- Get rid of it. - Shit.
嗨 是凯特
Hey,it's Kat.
听着…怎么回事?
Listen... what the hell?!
等一下 不是说你
Just wait. Not you.
我想 我们得停下来检查一下车 因为…
I think we better pull over and check the car,because...
凯柏莉 这车没事
Kimberly,the car is going to be fine.
你爸爸没事 你也会没事
Your dad's going to be fine,you're going to be fine.
知道吗?
Okay?
你看那个人
Look at that guy.
他在喝啤酒呢
He's drinking a beer.
对 他喝酒会自律的
Oh,yeah,that's real responsible.
你听说过臭氧层吗? 混蛋
You ever hear of the ozone layer,arsehole?!
怎么样 我正系着安全带呢
What? I'm wearing my seatbelt.
想撞我啊 婊子
You're gonna bust me,bitch?!
狗娘…
Son of a...
养的
bitch.
啊 真他妈的见鬼!
Fuck!
- 我的天哪! - 小心点!
- Oh my God! - Watch out!
- 停车! - 哦 我的天哪!
- Stop! - Oh my God!
- 小心! - 啊
- Watch out! - Aaah!
奇娜?
Shaina?
我出不来了!
I can't get out of here!
救救我啊!
Help me!
喔 冷静点 凯米 你第一次开车?
Oh,easy,Kimmy. First year of driving?
丹尼尔 要不要帮帮你妈妈?
Yo,Dano,shouldn't we help your mum?
好孩子 你去吧 没人阻拦的
Good one,man. You're hilarious.
连环相撞 连环相撞
Pileup! Pileup!
- 哦 天哪! - 什么?
- Oh my God. - What?
这里将会发生大车祸
There's going to be a huge accident.
我们都会死的 我看到了
We're all gonna die! I just saw it.
好 我来开车
That's it. My turn to drive.
- 不 我说的都是真的 - 凯米 哪里不对劲?
- No,I'm serious. - Kim,what's wrong?
- 你在干什么? - 我的天
- What are you doing? - Oh my God.
…180次航班空难周年纪念今晚8点
...of Flight 180 will be held at 8:00 P.M. Tonight...
在亚伯拉罕中学礼堂举行
at the Mt Abraham high school auditorium.
"通往地狱的高速公路"
"Highway to hell..."
"通往地狱的高速公路"?
"Highway to hell"?
我行驶在通往地狱的高速公路…
I'm on a highway to hell...
好了 凯柏莉 你别吓我了
Okay,Kimberly,you're scaring me.
- 绿灯意味着可以走了 凯米 - 是啊
- Green means go,Kimmy. - Yeah.
你脑子有问题了? 你在干什么?
Are you out of your friggin' mind? What the hell are you doing?
他妈的怎么了 凯柏莉?
What the fuck,Kimberly?
怎么回事?
What's this?
凯柏莉 你得冷静点
Kimberly,you just got to breathe.
妈的 巡警来了 我们溜吧
Oh,shit,shit. Five-O's coming. Let's fucking roll.
- 什么? - 哦 上帝
- What? - Oh my God.
你知道我身上有多少大麻吗?
Do you know how much fucking weed I have on me? Huh?
闭嘴 丹尼尔! 冷静点
Okay,Dano,just shut up! Just stay cool.
妈的 我得蹲监狱了 我得蹲监狱了
Oh,fuck. I'm going to jail. I'm fucking going to jail.
怎么回事啊?
What's going on here?
这里会出现汽车连环相撞
I think there's going to be a huge pileup.
我看见的
I saw it.
到处是尸体
There were bodies everywhere.
还有木头… 我看见了的
There were logs... I saw it.
快出事了
It just happened.
小姐 你能下车吗
Alright,miss,I'd like you to please step out of the vehicle.
靠边点
Just pull over!
我知道 宝贝 妈妈也很饿了
I know,Mummy's hungry,too.
快点
Come on.
快点啊!
Come on!
见鬼
Oh,fuck this.
我去看一下 然后我们就走
I'm going to get this and we're going to go.
妈的
Fuck.
这到底是怎么回事啊?
What the hell is going on up there?
对不起
Excuse me!
这里可以绕道吗?
Is there any way that we could drive around?
- 我去要送货… - 你回车里吧
- I have a delivery... - You need to get back into your vehicles.
- 快把车开边点… - 马上回去!
- Just move it... - Now!
就是那辆车!
That's it!
它会害死大家的
That's the truck that's going to kill everybody.
你得阻止它!
You need to stop that truck!
小姐 我再次对你说 你得冷静点!
I told you again,you have to calm down!
你干吗不听我的!
Why won't you listen to me?!
- 妈的! - 哦 我的天哪
- Fuck! - Oh my God.
我是13号 请求医疗救援
This is unit 13 requesting medical assistance
这里发生了严重车祸…
and backup for a major traffic accident...
凯柏莉 怎么回事?
Kimberly,what's going on?
不!
No!
听着 这姑娘真的吓坏了
Listen,sir,this girl is really freaked out.
你都想不到…
In fact,all of them are...
- 他们多么被吓坏 - 吓坏了?
- scared as you can imagine. - Scared?!
那些狗娘养的是世界上最幸运的人
These people are the luckiest sons of bitches on the planet.
你看这个家伙 艾文·刘易斯…
Get this guy,Evan Lewis...
昨天刚中了彩票
yesterday the kid wins the lotto.
今天又躲过此劫
Today,some loony bitch blocks traffic
好几年来最严重的连环相撞事故
and he avoids the worst pileup in years.
我要是这么"不幸"就好了
I should be so damnunlucky.
你去搞定其他人
Go babysit the rest of them.
我来搞定刘易斯 一会就完
I'll be done with Lewis in a minute.
打扰一下…
Hey,excuse me...
我们会尽最大的努力
We're trying to do the best we can.
我们会尽快让你们走的
We're going to get you out of here as soon as possible.
我只是觉得这都是胡说
I just think it's a bunch of bullshit.
听我说 你一定会转变对这件事的看法
Listen,I know you've gone over all this
你刚和苏丁侦探谈过…
with Detective Suby...
但是 你能否告诉我 到底发生了什么事?
but would you mind telling me what happened?
就好像是我身临其境
It was like I was there.
我事前就感觉到可怕的事情将会发生
I knew something bad was going to happen even before it did.
- 但是我的感觉总是不那么确定 就好像是… - 就好像什么?
- I just felt wrong,just like... - Just like what?
我知道这种事听起来好像很不正常 但是…
Look,I know this sounds crazy but...
你们都听说过180航班飞机失事 是不是?
you guys all heard about Flight 180,right?
那个从下飞机的孩子?
The kid who got off the plane?
那刚好是一年前的今天的事
Well,it happened a year ago,today.
我的感觉跟他的一样
My premonition was just like his.
- 你到底想说什么? - 说清楚点
- What are you talking about? - Come on.
你一定听说过那个小孩子的事
You must have read about the kid
他梦见了飞机爆炸
who had a dream about a plane blowing up,
所以 他把他所有的朋友都从飞机上叫下来
so he got all his buddies off the plane
后来 飞机是不是就和他做的梦一样爆炸了?
and then the thing blew up just like in his dream?
- 是的 - 可是你是否知道后来发生的事情?
- Yeah. - But did you hear what happened after?
就是有一个女人去找了他 是不是?
So a month goes by,right?
一切看起来那么不可思议
Everything seems cool.
后来所有的生还者一个个相继死去
But then all the survivors start to die one by one.
当轮到你的时候 那么就得去死 是不是?
'Cause when your number's up,your number's up,right?
有人说 是死神在追寻他们
You know,some people even say that Death itself was stalking them,
然后一个个地杀死他们
hunting each one down
直到所有的人…全都死了为止
until they were all... dead.
算了吧
Please.
还有一个幸存者…
There was one survivor.
克莱尔·莱维斯在墙四周设置软垫之病室里
Clear Rivers is in a padded room
在斯托尼布鲁克研究院
at the Stonybrook Institution.
噢 这是个振奋人心的消息
Well,that's encouraging.
噢 这么说你是要我相信 你说的是真的了
Okay,you want me to believe that this is true,
就是说这种事会再度发生?
that this is happening all over again?
我甚至都不知道 为什么我们会在这里
I don't know why we're even here.
你要我干什么?
What do you want from me?
如果不是我迅速把你拉到一边
But if I was never meant to pull over,
那么我们一定会死在那次撞车事件中
we all should have died in that pileup.
这就是说 死神会再次袭击我们?
Which means Death could be coming for us.
噢 这么说…
Yeah,like,what if
我们和被诅咒有何分别?
we're all getting thatDifferent Strokes' curse or something?
我想你们都是肯定有的
I think you're all are certifiable.
我真不敢相信 我会听到这样的白痴话
I can't believe I've been listening to this crap.
快走 快走 汤姆
Let's go. Let's go,Tim.
卡朋特太太 请等等
Mrs Carpenter,please.
凯柏莉!
Kimberly!
噢 宝贝!
Oh baby!
- 你没事吗? - 对不起
- Are you okay? - I'm so sorry.
嘘 嘘
Shh,shh.
现在你们都可以走了 谢谢你们的合作
You can all go now. Thank you for your patience.
我能否问你一些事情?
Could I ask you something?
可以
Anything.
妈妈是否…
Did Mum ever have any...
你知道妈妈有过一些不祥的预感吗?
I don't know,weird feelings about anything?
你想说什么?
What do you mean?
比如说是幻觉或者是预感什么的
Like visions or premonitions.
宝贝 你真的没事吗?
Sweetie,are you sure you're okay?
爸爸 我知道这听起来很荒唐
Dad,I know this sounds crazy,
但是我真的很担心其他的人
but I'm really scared for the others.
我不知道 我真的有这种可怕的感觉
I don't know,I have this really bad feeling.
怕什么?
What?
事情一定还没有结束
It's not over yet.
天哪!
Jesus Christ!
见鬼!
Shit!
嗨 艾文 我是托妮
Hey,Evan,it's Tawny.
对不起 我没有给你打电话
Sorry I haven't called.
喂 听说你中了彩票
Hey,listen,I heard about your lottery win.
保持联系 给我打电话
Let's hook up. Call me.
耶
Yeah.
嗨 艾文 我是尼奇
Hi,Evan,it's Nikki.
去年我们在塔克晚会上见过面 是吗?
We met at Tucker's party last year?
我知道已经过去了有那么一点点时间 但是我还是在想你
I know it's been awhile,but I've been thinking about you.
我想向你说声祝贺
I just wanted to say congratulations.
记得给我回电话
So give me a call.
号码是555-0123 再见
555-0123. Bye.
见鬼
You little bastard.
他妈的
Shit.
出来 出来
Come on. Come on.
他妈的 他妈的
Fuck. Fuck.
出来!
Come on!
出来
Come on.
靠!
Fuck!
天哪!
Jesus!
啊!
Oh!
喂 我是艾文 我给你留言
Hey,this is Evan. Leave a message.
要是你在找里奇 我也不知道他在哪里
If you're looking for Rick,I don't know where he is,
我也不知道他什么时候回来 谢谢
and I don't know when he's coming back. Thanks.
艾文 回来的时候记得给我打电话 你他妈的真走运!
Evan,call me when you get in,you lucky fuck!
出来! 出来! 出来!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
啊!
Aah!
天哪!
Jesus!
出来了!
Come on.
啊!
Aah!
他妈的 我还真走运
Shit,I'm lucky.
啊!
Aah!
天啊 真他妈的疯狂
Jesus Christ!
不 妈妈
No,Mother,
随便换个台
just turn on any station.
噢 我不知道你为什么会错过了 整天都在播放这消息
Well,I don't know how you missed it,it's been on all day.
对 妈妈 看4频道吧
Yes,Mother,Channel 4 is fine.
行…就这里! 要走了 是不是?
Okay... here it is! I got to go,okay?
我要走了!
I got to go!
新闻重播
To recap our top story,
今天 23号公路堵塞了将近9个小时
Route 23 was backed up for almost nine hours today.
一场史无前例的连环撞车 据估计有18人遇难
A record-breaking pileup killed an estimated 18 people.
紧急援救队花了数个小时搜查事故现场
Emergency crews spent hours sifting through the wreckage
希望能从这次可怕的事件中寻找出幸存者
hoping to recover any survivors from this tragic collision.
到目前为止 警方拒绝透露遇难者的姓名
So far police are refusing to release the names of the victims
直到通报了其家属为止
until the families are notified.
高速公路的训练车摄像机
The camera of a highway patrol car
记下了这次让人震惊事故的发生过程
managed to catch this shocking footage.
- 一辆拖车… - 啊 天哪
- A semi comes... - Oh my God.
撞碎了一辆红色SUV小轿车
And smashes into a red SUV.
- SUV车的司机… - 啊 不…
- The driver of the SUV... - No,um...
别关
leave it.
…也许已经救了她的命
...may have saved her life.
他在最后的一秒钟把她拉开
He pulled her back at the last second
就在拖车撞上SUV的那一刻
just as the semi ploughed into the vehicle.
在SUV上的人…
The passengers inside the SUV...
哦! 哦! 你们看到没有? 他妈的 我在现场呢!
Oh,oh,oh! You guys see that?! Shit,I was there,baby!
另外一条消息 一场意外事故夺走了彩票中奖者的性命
In other news,a freak accident took the life of a lotto winner.
- 有朋友说艾文·刘易斯… - 喂 别吵
- Friends say Evan Lewis... - Hey,shh.
在赢得了25万美元之后 高兴到了极点
Was on top of the world after recently winning $250,000.
但是事发突然 刘易斯今天死了
But in tragic turn of events,Lewis died today
他公寓发生的了火灾 在他竭力逃离的时候
while trying to escape a fire in his apartment.
他使用紧急逃生梯逃了出来
He managed to make it out of the building,
但是 就在他刚跳下来的时候
but somehow the ladder on the fire escape
梯子落下来砸死了他
slipped and impaled him.
调查人声称刘易斯是当场死亡
Investigators believe Lewis died instantly.
进来
Come in.
嗨 老兄
Hey,buddy.
我想你把这些吃下 然后睡觉
I want you to take this so you can get some sleep.
明天去找牙医 我知道你会去的
And then tomorrow it's off to the dentist,which I know you love.
好了 睡觉吧
Now,get some rest.
- 妈妈! - 怎么了?
- Mum. - Yeah?
你觉得今天的事是不是很奇怪?
You think those guys were BSing us today?
是的
Yeah.
有些人只是神经过度紧张 就这么简单
Some people just need some rewiring,that's all.
关灯了
Lights out.
依照病人的要求
At the request of the patient,
你不能带任何尖锐物品进去
you'll relinquish any sharp objects
比如: 指甲剪 铅笔 钢笔
such as:nail files,pencils,pens,
安全笔 别针 项链
safety pins,bobby pins,your necklace,
火柴 打火机 皮带 皮带扣
matches,lighters,belts,belt buckles,
耳环 发卡 眼镜 珠宝
earrings,hair clips,glasses,shoelaces,
回型针 手表 小刀
paper clips,watches,money clip,pocket knives,
食物 饮料 钥匙 手机…
food,drinks,keys,cell phone...
你有没有带手机?
You have a cell phone on you?
毒药 药丸 其他药物
...poisons,pills,medications.
好极了 让我看看你的指甲
Great. And let me see your nails.
好了 我想现在可以了
Good. Then I think we're all done.
等等
Wait.
她是不是很危险?
Is she dangerous or something?
不 她还以为你很危险呢
No,honey,she expects you are.
不 不 不
No,no,no.
让他离开我 让他离开我!
Get him off me. Get him off me!
你们要把她在这地方关多久?
How long are they gonna keep her locked up like this?
由她决定 我想她是自愿的
Depends on her,I guess. She's voluntary.
- 克莱尔·莱维斯? - 别再靠近了
- Clear Rivers? - Don't come any closer.
他们告诉我 你跟23号公路车祸有关
They told me you had something to do with the crash on Route 23.
我不知道怎样说
Look,I don't know how to explain it,
但我在车祸发生前预感到了
but I saw the pileup before it happened.
我救了一些人
And I saved some people.
你认为死神在逼近你
And now you think Death is after you.
好样的
Nice work.
如果你真的是幸运的话 那么你就会和我一样在这里
Maybe if you're real lucky,you'll wind up in here with me.
还有别的什么事?
Anything else?
昨晚有一个人死的离奇
One of the people died in a freak accident last night.
其他人也有危险吗?
What if the other people are in danger,too?
如果你把他们列入名单 那么他们实际上已经死了
If you put them on the list,they're already dead.
名单? 什么名单?
List? What list?
死亡名单
Death's list.
180幸存者的名单
The survivors of Flight 180
奇怪的一个接一个死去
died in the exact order
他们本来就该在那次事件中死亡
they were originally meant to die in the plane crash.
那是死神最初的计划
That was Death's original design.
计划好了一份名单
The list.
本来应该是在那次坠机事件中死亡
I was supposed to die in that crash with my friends.
这么说 你是要告诉我 我是下一个该死的人了?
So you're telling me that I'm next?
你说过昨天晚上有人死了
You said someone else died last night.
这意味着已经有人干涉进来
That means someone must have intervened.
博格警官把我拖开 但是我的朋友死了
Officer Burke pulled me away from the crash that killed my friends.
恭喜
Congratulations.
你将会是最后一个
You'll be the last to go.
但是 你放心 一旦别的人都死了
But don't worry,once the others are dead,
死神就会来找你
it'll come back for you.
死神一直是这样做的
It always does.
这没有可能
This doesn't make sense.
你刚才说 你们按照原来的次序死去
You said that you die in the order you're originally meant to.
但我的朋友在我的预感里面 是最后死的 而不是第一个
But my friends died last in my premonition,not first.
等等
Wait.
后死?
Died last?
倒退型?
Backwards.
你肯定吗?
Are you sure?
在我的预感中
In my premonition
那个叫诺拉的女人和她的孩子都死了
that Nora woman and her kid died.
接着是艾文 然后是我和我的朋友
Then Evan,then me and my friends.
这事情怎么会发生在我身上?
Why is this even happening to me?
艾历克斯也经常这么问他自己
That's what Alex used to ask himself.
那我该怎么办?
So,what am I supposed to do?
克莱尔
Clear.
注意一些迹象
Watch out for the signs.
什么?
What?
你有没有一些不祥的预兆?
Have you ever seen anything creepy or ominous?
反映在你眼帘里的相反事情?
An in-your-face irony kind of thing?
收音机上的歌曲
The songs on the radio.
对了 还有啤酒运输车上的司机 还有路上看到的一切
Yeah,the guy in the beer truck,everything on the road.
那就别忽略了
Well,don't ignore it.
记往那些征兆 那可以保住你的命
Recognising those signs usually means the difference between life and death.
你得帮帮我
You got to help me.
我没必要这么做
I don't have to do anything.
可天机是你泄漏的
But you beat it.
看看周围吧
Take a look around.
我泄漏什么天机了 凯柏莉?
What did I beat,Kimberly?
要是你明智的话 你就能自救 别人还是算了吧
If you were smart,you'd save yourself and just forget about the others.
你怎么能这么说呢? 你有责任的
How can you say that? You have a responsibility.
我的朋友都死了
My friends are dead.
所以我能这么说
That's how I can say that.
当我对艾历克斯负责的时候 这就是他的下场
This is what happened to Alex when I was responsible for him.
出去吧
Get out.
免得你伤害我或者你自己
Before you hurt me or yourself.
- 好吧 知道吗? - 什么?
- Alright,you know what? - What?
我觉得你是个胆小鬼
I think you're a coward.
你之所以躲到这来
You hide out in here because you're
是因为你倍受谴责 自私自利 不肯帮助其他人
too damn bitter and selfish to help any other person.
在我看来 你已经死了
In my opinion,you're already dead.
我昨晚一直给你打电话
I tried calling you last night,
可你爸爸说你在睡觉
but your father said you were sleeping.
- 艾文·刘易斯死了 - 知道了
- Evan Lewis is dead. - Yeah.
对 我今天早上不停接到事发现场的人打来的电话
I've been getting calls all morning from everyone who was on the on-ramp.
今晚我们在我家聚在一起
We're meeting tonight at my apartment.
慢着…你相信所有这些死亡传说?
Wait,so... you believe all this Death stuff?
开始我是不信的
Well,at first,no,I didn't.
直到去年我被派去
Until last year when I was dispatched
搜寻180次航班的幸存者
to clean up one of the Flight 180 survivors.
清理现场…
Clean up,I don't...
- 你看到了吗? - 看到什么?
- Did you see that? - See what?
- 鸽子 - 鸽子?
- Pigeons. - Pigeons?
- 这是一种迹象 - 什么迹象?
- It's a sign. - A sign of what?
如果克莱尔估计得对的话
If Clear's right about the order,
诺拉和汤姆就要被鸽子袭击了
then Nora and Tim are going to be attacked by pigeons.
我不明白
I'm not following you.
他们是死亡名单上下一个目标
They're next on Death's list.
要是我们找不到他们 他们会死的
If we don't find them,they're going to die.
汤姆 医生准备好了
The doctor's ready for you,now.
要是他给我带上氧气罐
If he gives me the gas
等到我醒来时 裤子被脱掉的话…
and I wake up with my pants unbuttoned...
- 那我们就不付钱 - 汤姆
- we ain't paying. - Tim.
来了 汤姆 昨天你出什么事了?
There you are. What happened to you yesterday,Tim?
我们都想你了
We missed you in here.
我们在23号公路上被耽搁了
We got hung up by that accident on Route 23.
天啊 你没事真是走运
Good Lord. How lucky that you're okay.
你妈妈说你最近牙疼
Your mum says you've been having some pain lately.
也不是
Not really.
我有点失望 汤姆
I'm disappointed,Tim.
你妈妈知道你抽烟了吗?
Does your mum know you've been smoking?
好了 这颗牙齿要修补一下
Yeah,that one's going to have to be filled.
真该死 那些鸽子
Damn those pigeons.
要我换多少次玻璃 这些该死的鸽子才肯罢休?
How many times am I going to have to replace those goddamn windows?
这样会有点疼
This will only sting for a moment.
张开嘴巴
Open big.
再大点
Little bit wider.
大点
Wider.
好
Okay.
天啊
Oh God.
他们怎么会指望我…
How do they expect me to...
带上氧气罐吧
Would you rather just have the laughing gas?
- 对 - 好
- Yeah. - Okay.
吉恩 进来帮帮我
Jean,I'm going to need you in here.
说大声点 这里很吵
You'll have to speak up,there's too much noise.
什么? 我听不见
What?! I can't hear you!
抱歉 您说什么
Excuse me,what?!
对 下午两点 第六个
Yes,the sixth at 2:00 P.M.
吉恩 我们开始了
Jean! Let me get this started.
汤姆 你会保持清醒的 不过会觉得有点头晕
Tim,you'll be awake,a little groggy,
千万别动来动去
but you're not going to be able to move much.
好的 谢谢你 好 调头
Okay,great,thanks. Alright,turn around.
清洁工说他们在14楼埃利斯诊所
The cleaning lady said they're at the Ellis Medical Complex off of 14th.
妈的
God damn it anyway.
- 好了 - 没有盒子!
- Okay,I got it. - I can't find a box!
别又来了 当心
Not again. Careful.
好了
There we go.
吉恩 汤姆情况怎样?
Jean,how's Tim doing in there?
他是怎么说你牙齿的?
What did he say about your tooth?
- 他说… - 我不记得了
- Did he say... - I can't remember.
- 诺拉! - 鸽子!
- Nora! - The pigeons!
什么? 鸽子?
What? Pigeons?
孩子 孩子!
Hey,whoa,whoa! Kid,kid!
- 不! - 汤姆!
- No-oo! - Tim!
当心!
Look out!
- 退后 退后! - 不 不!
- Stay back,stay back! - No! Please,no!
诺拉不来了 她不肯离开她的儿子
Nora's not coming. She won't leave her son.
- 不行 她是下一个… - 现在 我想她已经不在乎
- No,but she's next... - Right now I don't think she cares.
怪事又发生了 对不对?
This is really happening again,isn't it?
真希望我们能及时赶到
I hoped we'd get there
这样他们就会没事了
and they'd be fine,
克莱尔·莱维斯说的都是鬼话
and Clear Rivers was just full of shit,
艾文·刘易斯是因为突发的意外而死
and Evan Lewis' death was just some freak accident.
可我们都要死了 对不对?
But we're all going to die,aren't we?
我好害怕
I'm so scared.
我知道你不想这样…
I know you didn't ask for any of this...
我也不觉得你会就此罢休
but I don't think you have it in you to quit either.
又一个人刚刚死掉
A second one just died.
年仅15岁的孩子
A 15-year-old kid.
希望你准备好了
I hope you're ready for this.
就是这里
It's this way.
这个家伙怎样帮我们?
How is this guy going to help us anyway?
他好像知道更多关于死亡的乱七八糟的东西
He seemed to know a hell of a lot more
他就是不肯告诉我们
about Death than he ever told us.
不先敲门吗?
Shouldn't we knock first?
他知道我们来了
He probably already knows we're coming.
你好 克莱尔
Hello,Clear.
我已经等你很久了
I've been expecting you.
天啊
Oh my God.
- 是艾文·刘易斯 - 是来要我脑袋的吗?
- That's Evan Lewis. - Come to pick my brain?
问一个很简单的问题 我们不会打扰你和你的新朋友
Just a simple question and we'll leave you alone with your new friend.
死了…
Dead...
还新鲜
yet still fresh.
听着 我们大老远开车到这来
Look,we drove a long way to get here,
如果你碰巧能帮我们如何阻止死亡的话
so if you happen to know how to stop Death,
就请你高抬贵手 告诉我们吧
it would be really great if you told us.
你们骗不了死神
You can't cheat Death.
- 你们逃不出死神的魔爪 - 狗屁
- There are no escapes. - Bullshit.
你告诉过我 死神有个独特的构思
You told me Death has a distinct design.
可艾历克斯和我欺骗死神已经不止十几次了
But Alex and I cheated Death,not once but dozens of times.
构思是有缺陷的 可以被识破
The design is flawed,it can be beaten.
现在你玩火自焚了
Such fire in you now.
人死之前
People are always most alive
是那么的生机勃勃
just before they die.
你们不这么认为吗?
Don't you think?
求你了…
Look,please...
要是你知道能帮助我们的办法
if you know of anything that could help us,
你会受到什么伤害呢?
what harm could it do?
只有新生可以打败死亡
Only new life can defeat Death.
这是什么意思?
What the hell does that mean?
古人云: 万物皆有平衡
Some people say there's a balance to everything.
有生必有死
For every life there's a death,
有死必有生
and for every death there is a life.
新生命的来临
But the introduction of life that was not meant to be,
能使死亡名单失效
that can invalidate the list,
迫使死亡开始新生
force Death to start anew.
你应该找寻迹象…
You have to follow the signs...
凯柏莉
Kimberly.
你怎么知道我的名字?
How do you know my name?
- 哇! - 等一下
- Whoa! - Wait a second.
"新生打败死亡"? "跟随征兆"?
"New life defeats death"? "Follow the signs"?
那个家伙你是在哪找来的?
Where did you find that guy?
还以为他会帮我们呢
I thought he was supposed to help us,
谁知道他奚落我们
not freak us out.
你他妈的想死啊?
What the fuck are you thinking?!
我想舔我的鸡巴 婊子
I'm thinking suck on my junk,bee-atch.
小烂仔
Little punk.
怎么回事?
What is it?
你看到什么了?
What did you see?
你得告诉我们 你看到什么了?
You have to tell us,what did you see?
凯柏莉 看着我! 你一定得告诉我们
Kimberly,look at me! You have to tell us.
你到底看到什么了!
What did you see?!
我在一辆白色的货车上
I was driving a white van.
不知道怎么回事 一定是我失去了控制
I don't know,I must have lost control,
我冲到了湖里
because I crashed into a lake.
- 我溺水了 - 你在哪?
- And I drowned. - You were there?
事实上 我能感觉到湖水的味道
I can practically taste the water in my mouth.
慢着 还记得在车祸现场?
Wait,remember,the on-ramp?
当时有个怀孕的妇女驾驶白色的送货车
There was a pregnant woman in a white delivery van.
他说只有新生能打败死亡
He said only new life can defeat death.
要是她生下那个
If she gives birth to a baby
应该在车祸中死去的孩子…
that would've died in that car crash...
新鲜的灵魂绝不是死亡的征兆…
a brand new soul that was never part of Death's design...
他会毁掉整个死亡名单
It throws the whole list out of whack
然后我们就从一段清白的历史生存下去
and we start over with a clean slate.
- 好像着点边了 - 还有什么意思?
- It seems like a reach,don't you think? - What else could it mean?
我们得找到那个孕妇的电话号码
We have to find the pregnant lady's number.
我没有啊 她没来过警察局
I don't have it. She never came to the station.
我们得警告她溺水的事 这样她就能活着产下孩子
We have to warn her about the lake so she can stay alive to have the baby.
- 这样话 会容易点 - 我们怎么找她呢?
- That'll be an easy conversation to have. - How are we gonna find her?
全州有几千部这样的白色货车
There could be thousands of white vans in the state.
嘿!
Hey!
我是警察啊 不记得了?
I'm a cop,remember?
慢着 就是这部车
Wait,that's it.
找到了
Got it.
有了车牌号 我就可以发出通告了
With the plate number I can put out an APB.
好了
Here we go.
这部车是辆配货车
The vehicle is a delivery van
车主是玛库桑德·依莎贝拉·休顿
registered to Marcus and Isabella Hudson.
我们很快就能找到她
We should pick them up pretty quickly.
走吧 我们找人去
Come on,let's get to the meeting.
先别关门!
Hey,hold the door!
放我的鞋子进来!
Hey,let go of my shoe!
我的鞋!
Give me my shoe!
早在两周前我给经理报告了 告诉他这该死的电梯缓冲器了
I wrote to management two weeks ago about these friggin' bumpers.
是狗屎吗? 老兄
Is that dogshit,dude?
你脸上有…
Oh,you got something on your...
还在呢 来 我帮你擦
It's still there,bro'. Here,I can get it for you.
不了 没事
No,it's alright.
要是你不介意的话 我可以帮你擦嘛
I'll do it if you want me to do it.
让我…我来擦好了
Just let... I'll... Let me do it.
什么?
What?
嗨 你好吗?
Hey,man,how you doing?
有面包车的消息吗?
Listen,any word on that white van yet?
好的 我们继续查吧
Okay,keep checking.
谁带来镇定剂?
Does anybody have a Valium?
哦 是的
Oh,yeah.
给
Here.
你可以服用一半
You're just going to want to take half of that.
让他们来吧
Keepem coming.
如果你说是真的
If what you're saying is true,
那我就是下一个
that means I'm next.
别瞎说 胡闹
This is crazy,people,come on.
开始死神走向我们
First Death is stalking us,
现在是前兆吗? 什么?
and now premonitions? What?
你不是下一个 诺拉
You're not next,Nora.
谁也不必成为下一个 重要的是
Nobody has to be next. That's the point.
我们需要彼此帮助才能躲过此难
We need to help each other in order to get through this.
这不会是真的
This cannot be happening.
因为我的事业刚到顶峰
See,because my career is at a peak
而且刚找到一个好男人
and I finally met a quality guy.
我刚买房子
I just bought a house.
你如果闭嘴就能活着
Maybe if you shut the fuck up,you'll live.
就像我听取你的意见
Like I'm going to take advice from you.
好的 如果你们知道要寻找什么
Okay,look,if you know what to look for,
你们就有一个成功的机会
you have a fighting chance.
如果我打电话说地铁…
If I call and say,I don't know... subway...
那么就更快去高速公路
Get to a high-rise fast.
一个没有地铁道地方
A place where no subway could ever possibly go.
明白吗?
Get it?
好的 你们听好…
Okay,you guys,listen...
就因为凯柏莉一个人有预感
just because Kimberly has these visions,
但这不是说我们全部都不能
it doesn't mean we're not all capable
看到一些特殊的迹象
of seeing signs to some extent.
好了 好了
Okay,okay,look.
你们只是在胡说
I gotta call bullshit.
我已经坐在这里听了
I mean,I've sat here and listened
你们所有的理论 所有的故事
to all your theories and all your stories,
我想这全是胡说
and I think it's just all bullshit.
随便你怎么说!
Call it what you want!
- 我会让你好好地活下去的 - 亲爱的 我活得很好!
- It'll keep your arse alive. - Darlin',my arse is alive!
整天都好
Has been all day.
除你外没有人在追杀我们
There is nobody after us but you,
你让我们发疯
trying to make us all crazy.
又来了
I should have seen that coming.
对
Yeah.
如果你是下一个
If Death is out to get you,
你远离我们
why don't you get the hell away from us?
她是唯一以前经历过的
She's the only one that's dealt with this before.
从现在开始我们需要留心
We need to look out for each other from now on.
轮流休息
Sleep in shifts.
我们需要在危险的地方注意安全
We need to safe-proof this death-trap.
小姐 请你暂时离车
Get you to step out of the van,miss?
你在开玩笑吗?
Are you kidding me?
- 我做错了什么? - 有人报警说这辆车被偷了
- What did I do? - This vehicle's been reported stolen.
哦!
Ohh!
烦透了 我出去抽烟
Screw this. I'm going for a smoke.
不 不 不…外面不安全
No,no,no,it's not safe out there.
反正诺拉在我前面
So,Nora's got to bite it before me anyhow,huh?
哦 你们一点幽默感都没有
Oh,you people have no sense of humour.
诺拉 你还好吧?
Nora,you okay?
四年前我的丈夫死了
Four years ago my husband died.
现在轮到汤姆 我什么都没有了
Now Tim. There's nothing left for me.
别这样说 好吗?
Don't say that,okay?
如果现在是我去天堂…
If it is my time to go and be in heaven...
和家人见面的时候 我可以接受
with my family,I can accept that.
你应该相信我 我们可以战胜死亡
You got to trust me. We can fight this.
如果我们能坚持长久在一起
If we just stick together long enough
如果我们能找到那个婴儿…
for her to have her baby...
原谅我 我得去计划葬礼
If you'll excuse me,I have a funeral to plan.
诺拉
Nora.
你在干什么?
What do you think you're doing?
- 完成了 结束了 - 别走尤金
- I'm finished. I'm out. - Don't leave,Eugene.
听着
Look,look.
我自己把握自己的生命 行了吗?
I control my life,alright?
我不信什么死亡名单
Not some crazy list that Death has put together.
我会把这话刻在你坟前
I'll be sure to carve that into your tombstone.
随你怎么说 你们会吓着这些人的
Whatever. You may be able to scare these people,
- 我才不信 - 你们小心点
- I'm not buying that shit. - Be careful,man.
- 嗨 - 什么?
- Hey. - What?
就算你不相信 把这个给诺拉
Even if you don't believe,give this to Nora.
我要把这个放在…
I'm just going to put this in the...
橱子
closet.
对不起
Sorry.
哇
Whoa.
一个带着钩子的人?
Man with hooks?
一个带着钩子的人
Man with hooks.
嗨 我想我看到一个带钩子的人了
Hey,I think I see a man with hooks.
这是…
Is that...
- 迹象吗? - 我的天啊
- a sign? - Oh my God.
- 你们看到了吗? - 没错
- Do you guys see that? - He's right.
- 电话 - 该死的
- The phone. - Shit.
妈的
What the fuck?
- 哈罗? - 诺拉!
- Hello? - Nora!
- 你是谁? - 你听得见吗!
- Who is this? - Can you hear me?!
伯克警官 我…
Officer Burke,I can't...
我听不见! 什么!
I can't hear you! What?!
他…说什么!
What does he... What?!
一个带着钩子的人要杀你
A man with hooks is going to kill you.
- 什么 什么? - 噢…
- What,what? - Oh...
什么事 诺拉?
What is it,Nora?
不!
No!
- 等等 等等! - 放开!
- Wait,wait! - Let go!
等等 诺拉!
Wait,wait,Nora!
- 让我出去! - 别这样好吗?
- Get me out of here! - Will you stop it?!
我来帮你!
Let me help!
放开我!
Let me go!
Let go of me!
凯特!
Kat!
救我!
Help me!
- 等等! - 我不想死!
- Wait! - I don't want to die!
放我走
Aah! Let me out of here.
知道了 谢谢 他们找到了面包车
I got it,thanks. They found the van.
伊莎贝拉在格林五德湖警察局 有人看护着
Isabella's being held at the Greenwood Lake sheriff's station.
我自己把握生命!
I'm in control of my life!
- 该死的! - 尤金 怎么了?
- Kiss my arse! - Eugene,what is it?
- 我自己把握生命! - 怎么了 尤金?
- I control my life! - What happened,Eugene?
- 你们听到的 你们这帮混蛋 - 冷静点
- You hear me,you Reaper cocksucker?! - Calm down.
- 怎么了? 诺拉在哪? - 滚开!
- What happened? Where's Nora? - Back the fuck up!
- 别激动! - 滚开!
- Whoa,whoa,okay! - Back the fuck up!
尤金 怎么了? 告诉我们发生了什么事
Eugene,what's wrong? Just tell us what happened.
好了 把枪给我 尤金
Alright,give me the gun,Eugene.
- 给我枪 - 不! 不!
- Give me the gun. - No! Fuck no!
尤金 你冷静点 好吗?
Eugene,you just got to relax,bro',okay?
你需要冷静下来
You just got to calm down,man.
给我枪 给我枪 尤金!
Give me the gun. Give me the gun,Eugene!
- 不 不! - 别 别这样!
- No,no,no,no! - Don't do it! Don't do it!
- 我不能这样出去 - 嗨 尤金 不!
- I ain't going out like that. - Hey,Eugene,no!
- 该轮到我了! - 我的天!
- On my terms! - Oh my God!
你听到我的!
You hear me!
我的天!
God!
哦!
Oh!
你没有上膛吗?
You don't keep it loaded?
- 也许全是哑弹 - 一梭六发子弹?
- Maybe they're all duds. - Six in a row?
决不可能
Never. That's impossible.
这还没有轮到他死
It wasn't his turn to die.
我们赶快找到那个怀孕的妇女好吗?
Can we find the pregnant woman,now,please?
这样安全吗?
Is this safe,guys?
我是说 车里的人已经疲惫不堪了
I mean,someone in this car is about to get whacked.
不会发生什么事吧? 是他
Do the rest of us really feel like sitting next to him?
还是她?
Or her?
她有希望的
Hopefully her.
好了 我们大家不要慌
Okay,guys,let's not panic.
- 伊莎贝拉很安全 - 你怎么知道?
- Isabella's safe. - How do you know?
你说过她把车开到湖里去了
You said she was going to drive into a lake.
如果她受警方保护怎么可能呢?
How can she if she's in protective custody?
看看我
Look at me.
来
Come on.
我看起来象是
Does it look like I'm in the condition
偷车的人吗? 真是神经病
to commit grand theft auto? This is insane.
听着 星期一早上之前
Look,hopefully the district judge
会给你一个公正的说法 好吗?
will have it all sorted out by Monday morning,okay?
马特斯
Marcus.
马特斯 马特斯
Marcus,Marcus.
等我出去了 我要控告他…
When I get out of here,I am going to sue his...
- 我的天 - 怎么了?
- Oh my God. - What,what now?
我的羊水破了
My water just broke.
- 什么? - 我的羊水破了 我要生了
- What? - My water,it just broke.
- 我要生孩子 - 不 在这不行
- I'm gonna have my baby. - No,not here.
- 不 你不能这样做 - 别愣在那!
- No,you can't do this to me. - Don't just stand there!
- 快送我去医院! - 再让我想想!
- Get me to a hospital! - Give me a second to think!
我不能在监狱里生孩子!
I am not going to have my baby in a jail cell!
送我去医院!
Get me to the hospital!
好 好!
Okay,okay!
培里长官 这是代理人亚当斯 回来
Sheriff Perry,this is Deputy Adams,come back.
天哪 我要车 培里长官 我需要车!
God,I need the car! Sheriff Perry,I need the car!
我的面包车! 我的面包车! 用我的面包车!
My van! My van! Take my van!
好的 好的
Okay. Okay.
好 我们走 我们走
Yeah,we'll go. We'll go.
我们走
Yeah,we'll go.
快点 快点!
Come on,come on!
你们想听点疯狂的事吗?
Y'all want to hear something crazy?
这不是我第一次死里逃生了
It's not the first time I cheated Death.
一个孩子带着刀来到学校…
A kid came to school with a knife...
杀了他的老师
killed his teacher.
那个老师本应该就是我
Teacher would have been me,
但是我两天前调离了那所学校
but I was transferred to another school two days before.
那真是太离奇了
That's fucking weird,man.
想听更离奇的事吗?
You want weird?
去年我和我的搭档准备出行
Last year my partner and I were heading out
此时有个打来电话说火车失事
when a call came in about a train wreck.
弗兰克让我独自去处理
Frank decided to let me handle it alone.
结果他当晚殉职了
He died that night in a shootout.
如果电话晚打10秒钟
If that call had come in just 10 seconds later,
我也会死
I'd be dead,too.
我的天哪
Oh my God.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我也有一个
It's just I got one,too.
去年五月我想在宾夕法尼亚
Okay,so last May I'm supposed to go and stay
一家低档旅馆往宿
at this cheesy little bed and breakfast in Pennsylvania.
没有人知道那里发生煤气泄漏
Anyhow,there's this major gas leak that no one knows about,
晚上所有的旅客都死了
and all the guests suffocated during the night.
怎么样了?
So what happened?
我不知道 我没有去那旅馆
I don't know. I never made it.
我坐的公交车撞了一个女孩
The bus I was on splattered some girl all over the road.
被撞地点在亚伯拉罕?
Was that in Mt Abraham?
是的 你怎么知道?
Yes. How did you know?
你坐的公交车撞死了特里·泰莉
That bus you were on killed Terry Chaney.
她也在180航班
She was supposed to die on Flight 180.
你们听说过巴黎剧院倒塌
Hey,do you guys remember that theatre in Paris
导致所有在场人员死亡?
that collapsed last year and killed everybody inside?
我本来买了票去的
Well,I had tickets to go.
但是我只能在巴黎呆一晚
But one night I'm in Paris
我还不如见识一下
and I'm just tripping on acid
巴黎的夜生活轻松一下
and sipping lattes and such.
但是突然
And then all of a sudden
一个人
this dude out of nowhere
被广告牌砸死了
just gets whacked by this falling sign.
- 卡特 - 等等
- Carter. - Wait,wait,wait.
那个死去的老师叫瓦尔·莱温顿
The teacher I replaced,her name was Val Lewton.
她来自亚伯拉罕 死于爆炸
She was from Mt Abraham. She died in an explosion.
该死的 那个关于火车失事的电话
Shit. The call about the train wreck
救了我的命…
that saved my life...
那晚死掉的是比利·希契科克
that was the night I scraped up Billy Hitchcock.
等一下 这些人都是谁?
Wait a minute. Who are these people?
这些都是180航班的乘客
The people who got off of Flight 180.
都是我的朋友
They were my friends.
凯柏莉 告诉我们你发生了什么事
Kimberly,tell us what happened.
大约一年前 我妈和我去商场买东西
About a year ago my mum and I were at the mall.
我本来和妈妈去拿车
I was supposed to meet her outside,
但被记者截停访问
but I got caught up watching this news report
关于年轻人自杀的事
about some kid that committed suicide.
我一直在想
I kept thinking,
怎么有人会在在浴缸里扼死自己?
'How can you strangle yourself in the bathtub?
真是蠢到头了
That's stupid.
感觉错了
It felt wrong.
然后…
And yet...
我听到几声枪响 于是我就跑出去看
I heard some gunshots and I ran outside.
原来是有几个孩子想偷我妈妈的车
Some kids were trying to steal my mum's car.
她尽力和他们搏斗 她很英勇
She tried to fight them off,she was a fighter,
最后他们杀了我妈妈
and they killed her.
葬礼过后 我一直在想 死的应该是我
After the funeral I kept thinking that it should have been me.
我猜大家都这么想
I guess everyone must think that.
可我猜 我是对的
But I guess I was right.
能不能快点? 再开快点?
Get there. Could you drive a little faster maybe?!
- 这已经是最快了 - 天啊!
- I'm going as fast as I can. - God!
乘了180航班
When we got off Flight 180,
不仅我们的命运都被改变了
it didn't just change our lives.
这还影响到和我们接触的
It affected everyone and everything
任何人和事
we've come into contact with since.
我恐怕听不懂你的意思
I'm not sure I'm understanding you.
本该死但我们却没死
Being alive after we were supposed to die,
引起一阵涟漪
it caused an outward ripple.
这违背了死神的计划
A rift in Death's design.
你是说 如果你没能生还…
So if you had never gotten off the plane...
我们可能早就死了?
we wouldn't be alive in the first place.
是的 这就是死亡顺序反过来的原因!
Yes,that's why Death is working backwards!
把所有薄弱点联系在一起
It's tying up all the loose ends,
一劳永逸的封住缺口
Sealing the rift once and for all.
妈的!
Oh,shit!
天啊!
Jesus Christ!
撑往! 撑往!
Hang on! Hang on!
- 大家都没事吧? - 天啊
- Is everybody alright? - Oh God.
天啊 尤金!
God,Eugene!
- 他呼吸不了了 - 我的腿!
- He can't breathe. - Oh,my legs!
别去 求你了
No,please.
- 孩子等不了了 - 我得去帮那些人
- It's not going to wait. - I got to go help those people.
你想让我在这里生下孩子吗?
Do you want to deliver this baby?
那些人能帮他们 我们走吧
Those people can help. Let's go.
亚当斯警官报告 一辆车辆
Officer Adams reporting a vehicle collision
在180英里处冲出9-A号公路
off 9-A at the 180 mile-marker.
派所有应急车到现场
Send all emergency vehicles to the scene.
- 我们得走了 快! - 好 好 好!
- We have to go. Go! - Okay,okay,okay!
好了! 好了! 我们走! 我们走!
Just... okay,okay! We're going! We're going!
- 轻点放 - 躺这里
- Easy,easy. - Here,here,here.
他的肺功能大概衰竭了
I think he has a collapsed lung.
- 大家都没事吧? - 叫救护车!
- Everyone okay? - Call an ambulance!
别抛下我们
Stay with us.
小伙子!
Hey,hey you!
过来 帮帮我
Hey! Come on. Help me out.
爆炸之前帮我逃出去 好吗?
You got to get me out of here before this thing explodes or something,okay?
没事的
I think it's okay.
我没闻到什么汽油味 也没有什么东西漏出来
I don't smell any gas and nothing's dripping.
好吧 帮我把木棍拉出来 快
Alright,get this thing off me. Just pull. Hurry.
- 好吧 - 当心 准备好了?
- Okay. - Be careful. Ready?
天啊!
Oh God,Jethro! Jesus Christ!
我完蛋之前我还要用我的腿的
I got to be able to use my legs when I'm done.
我…爸爸!
I'm so... Dad!
尤金 你会好起来的
Eugene,everything's going to be okay.
要是没有呼吸器 他会撑不往的!
If he doesn't get a respirator,he's not going to make it!
- 我们送你去医院 - 当心点!
- We're going to get you to the hospital. - Be careful with that!
检查好标准仪上的刻度 还要当心剂量!
Check the gauges on the regulator,and watch out for overdoses!
- 还要当心湖泊和水坑 - 你不能上车 小姐
- And look out for potholes and puddles. - You can't come in,miss.
还要当心电线!
And watch out for power lines!
当心!
Watch it!
你想找死吗 小家伙?
You trying to get yourself killed,little boy?
得想开点
You got to use your head,man.
把那辆面包车开过来
Get that news van back.
谢谢
Thanks.
好了 我们走
Okay,let's go.
她怎么啦?
How is she doing?
我想应该没事吧
I think she's going to be okay.
- 问你一个问题 - 什么?
- Can I ask you a question? - Yeah.
如果我死了…
When I die...
你会伤心吗?
is it going to hurt?
我不知道
I don't know.
然后你也会死 是吗?
You're going to die after me,right?
我想是吧
Yeah,I guess so.
你能拿着这些吗?
Would you take these?
如果我死了…
And if I die...
把我的这些毒品
would you throw out all my drugs
和色情书籍扔了
and my paraphernalia and my porno?
你知道的…
You know...
这些会让我妈妈心碎的
anything that's going to break my mum's heart.
求你了
Please?
谢谢
Thank you.
我是夏恩·加克博山
This is Cheyenne Jacobson
在基伯森农场为您报道
reporting live from the Gibbons farm.
皮瑞郡长 我是布鲁克警官
Sheriff Perry,Officer Burke here.
我想得知一些有关伊莎贝拉·休顿的消息…
I'm trying to get some information on Isabella...
她走了?
She did?
是吗? 好的 谢谢
Okay. Thanks. Great.
凯柏莉!
Kimberly!
她到医院去了 快要分娩了
Isabella's at Lakeview Hospital. They're prepping her for delivery.
- 我们得走了 - 那凯特怎么办?
- We got to go now. - What about Kat?
我和她谈谈
I'll go talk to her.
你好
Hi.
你们去找她吧 再把事情说清楚
Just find Isabella and get this thing over with,okay?
去吧 我没事的
Go on,I'll be fine.
- 劳里去哪里了? - 我不知道
- Where's Rory? - I don't know.
你们能安静点吗?
Could you be a little quieter with that thing,please?
好的 当然 我用安静档
Yeah,sure. I'll just put it on quiet mode.
那就好
That would be good.
劳里
Rory.
天哪!
Oh my God!
有人出来了!
Somebody get out there!
- 我们必须得赶到医院! - 用我的卡车吧!
- We have to get to the hospital now! - Well,take my truck!
钥匙在里面
The keys are in it.
凯柏莉!
Kimberly!
- 凯柏莉 - 你看到了什么?
- Kimberly. - What do you see?
- 我们要找什么? - 不在这
- What are we looking for? - It's not here.
这次不同
This one was different.
好像一辆面包车冲进了湖中
It was like the van crashing into the lake.
我梦见我在医院 我在叫喊
I was in a hospital,there was screaming
有个护士想掐死我
and a nurse was trying to choke me.
我看不到她的样子 但我看到她的名牌
I couldn't see her,but I could see her name tag.
就在我眼前 克劳吉安
It was right in my face. Kalarjian.
我想一个叫克劳吉安的护士想杀死伊莎贝拉
I think a nurse named Kalarjian is going to try and kill Isabella.
听着 伊莎贝拉 你不能再用劲了!
Listen to me,Isabella! I need you to stop pushing!
怎么了 我的孩子还好吗?
What's wrong? Is my baby alright?
你夹着他的颈子 孩子有危险
The cord's around the neck. This baby's in trouble.
今天在一场车祸中有两人丧生
A bizarre accident has left two people dead,
一个被车内的安全保护装置杀死
one of them killed by a safety device meant to protect us.
这个女人在安全气袋膨胀之后
Ironically,the woman was impaled through the head
在车内被戳穿了头颅
after her emergency airbag deployed.
她是在格林伍德发生车祸后被困在车里
She was trapped in her vehicle after it crashed into a field near Greenwood Lake.
突然安全气袋膨胀开…
Suddenly the airbag went off...
伊莎贝拉·休顿在哪个病房?
Isabella Hudson! What room is she in?
我们得做个紧急处理!
We may need to do a stat Caesarean!
快叫克劳吉安医生到这来!
Get Dr Kalarjian up here now!
克劳吉安医生 请到六号产房
Dr Kalarjian,code blue. Delivery room six.
我正在外面等
I'm just going to wait outside,
因为我就在到这里的路上
'cause I'm just really in the way here.
- 别离开我 - 好的 好的
- Don't you dare leave me! - Okay,okay.
你们去找伊莎贝拉!
You guys,get to Isabella!
我去找尤金!
I'm going to find Eugene!
克劳吉安医生 请到六号产房 亮了蓝灯
Dr Kalarjian,code blue. Delivery room six.
Dr Kalarjian,delivery room six. Code blue.
克劳吉安 这边 快点!
Dr Kalarjian,in here,hurry!
就是她
That's her.
等等 等等 等等
Wait,wait,wait!
宫缩停止了
Contractions have stopped.
得疏通产道
Arrest in descent halfway through the birth canal.
不良轨迹 缺氧
Bad tracing,it's losing oxygen.
线都变成扁平的了!
The cord's compressed!
- 低于40了 - 噢 天哪! 发生什么事了?
- Down to 40. - Oh God! What's happening?!
克劳吉安在哪里?
Where's Kalarjian?!
克劳吉安医生
Dr Kalarjian!
- 克劳吉安医生! - 现在不行 我没空
- Dr Kalarjian! - Not now,I'm busy.
- 怎么回事 - 警察 找你有事
- Ow! Hey! Hey! - Police business.
再用点劲
Just push a little more.
噢 不
Oh,no.
伊莎贝拉 孩子没事吧?
Isabella,is the baby okay?
对不起 你得离开这
I'm sorry. You can't be here.
- 我必须让你们离开 - 我们想知道…
- I have to ask you to leave. - I need to know...
我们想知道孩子是不是没事!
I need to know if the baby's alright!
是个男孩
It's a boy.
谢谢你 恭喜!
Thank you. Congratulations!
他们是谁?
Who the hell are they?
我的天
Oh my God!
- 克莱尔 - 我找不到尤金
- Clear. - I can't find Eugene.
- 别担心了 孩子出生了! - 一切顺利
- No,don't worry. She had the baby! - It's okay.
一切顺利 这都结束了
It's over. It's okay.
- 凯柏莉 - 你看到了什么?
- Kimberly. - What did you see?
我想她不应该死于那次车祸
I don't think Isabella was ever supposed to die in that pileup.
如此说来 那个湖是什么意思?
Then what's the premonition of the lake supposed to mean?
努力想一想
Try to remember.
一双血手 一个满手是血的人
Bloody hands. Someone with bloody hands.
尤金
Eugene.
只有新的生命才能击败死神 这到底什么意思?
Only new life defeats death. What is that supposed to mean?
你看到了心电图机 还有什么?
You saw an ECG machine and what else?
血淋淋的手 还有什么? 凯柏莉?
Bloody hands. What else did you see,Kimberly?
等等
Wait.
尤金
Eugene.
哦 不
Oh God,no!
血手
Bloody hands.
是我 梦见的是我自己
It's me. The premonitions are about me.
- 什么? - 车子坠毁了
- What? - Crash cart.
走 快推!
Let's go! Move it!
克劳吉安医生
Dr Kalarjian.
心电图机
ECG machine.
湖
The lake.
还有白色面包车
The white van.
你说什么?
What are you talking about?
新生命
New life.
什么意思?
What is it?
我知道如何才能挽救一切
I know what I have to do to save us.
- 我必须得死 - 你疯了啊
- I have to die. - No,that's crazy.
你不能放弃 我们必须战斗
You can't give up now. We have to fight this thing.
去找克劳吉安
Get Kalarjian.
只有新生命可以战胜死神
Only new life can defeat death.
如果我得去天堂…
If it is my time to go and be in heaven...
和家人会合 我接受
with my family. I can accept that.
第180次航班…
Flight 180...
我知道我该怎么做才能够救大家
I know what I have to do to save us.
还没有发现生还者
There are no known survivors.
我必须死
I have to die.
充电 放电
Ready and clear!
没效果!
Nothing!
充电 放电
Ready and clear.
没效果
Nothing.
- 快来 - 充电 放电
- Come on. - Ready,clear.
她活过来了!
She's back!
我注入了两毫克氧气
Epinephrine. Two milligrams,IV push.
我们要给她安装呼吸稳定器
I want her prepped and stabilised for ICU.
欢迎你回来
Welcome back.
你一段时间停止了呼吸
They lost you for a minute there.
嗨 我们成功了
Hey. We did it.
因为你 我们战胜了死亡
Thanks to you,we cheated Death.
你想来点白酒吗?
Would you like some wine?
谢谢 我更喜欢啤酒
I think I'll stick to our beer,thanks.
好的
Alright.
这真不错 基宾斯夫人
This is really great,Mrs Gibbons.
谢谢你邀请我们
Thank you so much for inviting us.
别客气了
It's our pleasure.
- 你最近怎么样 凯柏莉? - 还好
- How are you doing,Kimberly? - Good. Yeah.
这个夏天我过得很好
I had a fun summer.
我不知道是不是度过了这个夏天 我想一切都己恢复正常了
I don't know,I guess things are pretty much getting back to normal.
布莱恩 我想你还是去看看烧烤怎么样了
Brian,I think you better go check that barbecue.
嗨 小心点 那东西很危险
Hey,careful. Those things are dangerous.
没事的 我经历过更危险的
Trust me. I think I've been through closer calls.
我也是 老爸 你告诉他们那次采访车的事
Yeah,me too. Dad,you should tell them about the news van thing.
什么?
What's that?
布莱恩那天几乎被采访车撞了
Brian was almost hit by that news van that day in the field.
你的朋友劳里 在最后关头才把他拉出来
And your friend Rory,he pulled him back at the last second.
- 最终他获救了 - 皮特 你从来没跟我提过
- Saved his life. - You never told me that,Peter.
孩子 那次真是幸运
Boy,that was lucky.
布莱恩!
Brian!
《死神来了2》